https://mycountrymagic.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – My Country Magic
Skip to content
TradeSales TeamU-pickCommercial Pick
FacebookInstagram
Search for:
OUR PRODUCTSCOUNTRY MAGICDiscover The MagicTaste The ColoursOur BrandsWhere To Find UsPRODUCTSBlueberriesStrawberriesBlackberriesGrape TomatoesPotatoesOnionsBeansOUR RECIPESDELICIOUS INGREDIENTSTaste the Magic
Kale Fresh Role
Curry Vegetable Samosas
Crunchy Multi-Colored Beet Tacos
OUR FARM
ABOUT USExperience The MagicOur HistoryProduction On The FarmSustainabilityQuality & InnovationOur CommunitiesOur PeopleOur FacilitiesOUR GROWERSPreserve The MagicOUR BLOGMEDIATALK TO USREQUEST THE MAGICContact UsFAQWORK WITH US
Privacy Policycountrymagic2017-10-03T15:00:09+00:00
Privacy PolicyMy Country Magic is committed to respecting the personal privacy of individuals who visit our website. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices of the My Country Magic website.
My Country Magic does not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, e-mail or street address during your visit to its website. This information is only obtained if you supply it voluntarily, usually through commenting, contacting us via e-mail, or through the search function in the site.
All personal information you do provide is protected under the federal Privacy Act. This means that, at the point of collection, you will be informed that your personal information is being collected, the purpose for which it is being collected and that you have a right of access to the information. My Country Magic may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Questions or comments regarding this policy, or the administration of the Privacy Act in the My Country Magic website may be directed to marketing@mycountrymagic.com. If you are not satisfied that we have adequately respected your privacy, you may wish to contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner by calling 1-800-267-0441 or via the Internet at www.privcom.gc.ca.
Privacy PolicySite MapContact Us
Copyright 2020 Nova Agri | All Rights Reserved | Website by Windrose Web Design
FacebookInstagram
Toggle Sliding Bar Area
Welcome to Country Magic We are dedicated to producing quality Country Magic products that will be part of our customer’s healthy lifestyle.
Our primary crops include highbush blueberries, onions, potatoes, strawberries, lettuce and other greens—we are constantly introducing new items that will liven up your plate!
Contact Information
1225 Middle Dyke Rd. Centerville, NS. B0P 1J0
Canada
Phone: 1 (902) 582-1445
Email: novaagri@mycountrymagic.com
Go to Top
